[Music]
hey what's up welcome to every damn day
today we debate who is the best South
Park villain of all time but first let's
preview this week's episode of South
Park hey throw to it don't you wish you
had more quality one-on-one time with
your
phone odd by phone with parents and
relationships imagine being able to shut
them out for a little while Craig so you
can focus on what matters with Buddha
box you can cut out all the unwanted
noise not have to deal with
conversations that are of no interest to
you well I have to admit sometimes would
be a tweaker together it's it's like he
wants my attention all the time
but I'm about to blow y'all minds but
Cartman villain let's weigh it uh he's
cooked the kid fed him to his friends
he's also kind of racist I mean we've
heard how he talks to token I got to
always bring up token because he's the
only black guy on the show and I'm only
black on show I understand token but is
he the most evil of all time I don't
know just to make sure we we have a
unbiased debate today we're going to
have two guests on the show and they're
going to plead the case for who they
think is the most evil person on South
Park of all time is and I'm going to let
them introduce themselves yeah you know
what it is I'm here I'm new school Chris
you know what I'm saying doing what I do
you know what I'm saying cuz he trying
to tell me with young kids like I'm
trying to tell him he old flat out he
old my name is old school Chris and I'll
be speaking on behalf of Old South Park
you remember the good old days back when
it was cardboard cutouts and Chef was
just giving cookies to the kids y this
dude come on come on come on I want to
shout out you know what I mean any other
the seasons over season 17 that's when
the magic really came together all the
rest of that was practice you know what
I mean you know a before Beauty dog the
youth is wasted on the young
now my villain is as old as time itself
Satan oh he's the best all time villain
because he's oldest time
itself now take a
look if I go spend the night with Saddam
then it's over between me and Chris
Chris has been so nice to me and I know
Saddam will just hurt me
again maybe I'll just go talk to Saddam
I need closure yeah that's it I need
closure what am I doing what took you so
long baby Saddam I'm just here to talk
great let's
talk this B is comfy wfy Saddam I only
came here because I need closure sounds
fun you know me I'll try anything no
Saddam listen to me would you like a
drink maybe just a little one I have to
go back soon I need you to understand
that we can't be together anymore I need
you to not come by the condo and not try
to see see me Chris thinks we can all be
friends but I don't and I have to focus
on Chris now what is this these hotels
have all kinds of crazy channels Sadam
will you listen to me Chris is a great
person he's the one I want to be with
now really so then what are you doing
here I don't know about you but this
video is getting me pretty hot Sadam
here have another
drink oh oh God my head
drank too much
Chris oh no Satan on South par was the
most evil because he had a heart of gold
and I don't know if you notied I threw
in Saddam Hussein for free the thing
about Satan that makes him so great is
he can create evil from scratch he would
beat up Jesus sometimes you can't no man
should be laying hands on Jesus and plus
he cheated on his boyfriend and another
thing is anybody everybody knows if you
got horns and you're red you're evil
that's just the way I was RA Satan's
been around since the beginning of time
just like you huh let me show you who
the most evil thing ever are throw that
up remember which way we're going I
maybe hey hey remember the Ewok village
oh I maybe I may I
need a hang
on hey you shut the up yeah we're going
to kill you
[Music]
m oh remember this song sure I I love
this song it was fantastic
[Music]
yeah now that's evil the member bags are
evil cuz they play mind game there's
nothing more evil than your own thoughts
that's what they do they get you in a
place where you can't ever escape it and
blueberries blueberries themselves are
very popular fruit they're very cute and
adorable that's how they get you with
the real evil cuz they are choking hats
that's what I do they kill you from the
inside out you know something you know
remember B made me remember that I hate
old
but you're both wrong the most evil
villain of all time is Mr Garrison check
this out happy anniversary to
you happy anniversary to you cha cha cha
happy anniversary Mr President happy
anniversary to
you congratulations Mr President looks
like many more years of the same are to
come oh I don't think
so I think the next three years are
going to be even better
now that's evil this dude is on the same
evil scale as the Joker all right he
killed off Mr Hat he also has the worst
cartoon spray on tan I've ever seen and
he also made Cartoon Paul Ryan cry hands
down is Mr Garrison I hear old Chris he
talking about Satan new Chris talking
about as memberberries they all right
they look delicious to me you know I
mean and some of Y May thinking you had
a good point with cart let me know in
the comments talk to me I want to hear
what you guys to say I might respond to
some of y'all I know you need to like
comment and subscribe what to this
here every damn rock with it
[Music]